Elihu Thomson Papers 1865-1944 Mss.Ms.Coll.74
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Professional Correspondence, Ca. 1870-1937; 52 boxes; 26 linear feet
  - Carboid Oil-Less Bearing Company, Ltd., 1894; 1 item (Box Series I-8)
  - Carborundum Company, 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-8)
  - Carey, Thomas, 1921; 3 items (Box Series I-8)
    Bryn Mawr College
  - Carhart, Henry S., 1893-1905; 9 items (Box Series I-8)
    University of Michigan
  - Carichoff, E. R., 1904; 1 item (Box Series I-8)
  - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching, 1918; 1 item (Box Series I-8)
    Henry S. Pritchett
  - Carnegie Institution of Washington, 1916-1923; 2 items (Box Series I-8)
  - Carnegie Institution * Yerkes Observatory, 1903; 2 items (Box Series I-8)
    University of Chicago
  - Carnegie Technical School, 1904-1906; 7 items (Box Series I-8)
    A. J. Wurts
  - Carpenter, Arthur Howe, 1918; 1 item (Box Series I-8)
  - Carpenter Enamel Rheostat Company, 1895; 1 item (Box Series I-8)
  - Carpenter, Frank B., 1905; 1 item (Box Series I-8)
  - Carpenter, John F., 1897; 1 item (Box Series I-8)
  - Carrier, Sidney, 1930; 1 item (Box Series I-8)
  - Carroll, Dwight, 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-8)
    Lehigh University
  - Carsley, A., 1914; 1 item (Box Series I-8)
  - Carter, Kelso, 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-8)
  - Cartwright, W. J., 1919; 1 item (Box Series I-8)
  - Cartwright, William, 1926; 1 item (Box Series I-8)
  - Carty, John J., 1911-1923; 3 items (Box Series I-8)
    American Institute of Electrical Engineers
  - Cary, Arthur, 1913; 1 item (Box Series I-8)
  - Case, Andrew, 1897; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Case, Everett, 1930; 5 items (Box Series I-9)
    Central H.S.- Barnwell Fdn.
  - Case School of Applied Science * Department of Physics, 1923-1928; 7 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Casella, C. F. & Company, Ltd., 1912-1916; 2 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Cassier's Magazine, 1895-1904; 12 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Cassidy, John E., 1893; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Cataract Power and Conduit Company, 1897; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Catlin, R. M., 1903; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Cattell, J. McKeen, 1898-1910; 7 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Cavin, Samuel E., 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - C. E. Exploration Syndicate, Ltd., 1897; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Celebration of the Beginning of the Second Century of the American Patent System, 1891; 2 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Central High School, 1870-1939; 21 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Central High School * Associated Alumni, 1904-1934; 4 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Central High School * Barnwell Foundation, 1929-1935; 21 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Central High School. The Mirror, 1932; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Central Street School, 1917; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Century Magazine * The Electrical Engineer, 1896; 7 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Century of Progress, 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Certain, Mrs. Henry J., 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Chalmers, W. J., 1907; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Chamber of Commerce * Schenectady, 1936; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States of America, 1923; 2 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Chamberlain, G. N., 1915-1923; 3 items (Box Series I-9)
    American Institute of Electrical Engineers Synn Section1
  - Chamberlain, J. N., 1899; 3 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Chamberlain, T. C., 1928; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Chance Brothers & Company, Ltd., 1924; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Chance, G. Whitfield, 1894; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Chancellor, Eustathius, 1904; 2 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Chandler, Charles F., 1909; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Chaplin, E. D., 1908; 2 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Chapman Double Ball Bearing Company, 1902; 2 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Charitable Mechanics Association, 1906; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Charities and the Commons, 1906; 2 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Chase, George W., 1911; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Chatain, Henri G., 1913; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Chattanooga Chamber of Commerce, 1913-1916; 4 items (Box Series I-9)
    Kruesi, Paul J.
  - Chelmsford Grange, No. 244, 1917; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
    Frank Lupin
  - Chemical Abstracts, 1932; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
    W. A. Noyes
  - Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering, 1926; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Chesley, William S., 1930; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Chicago Daily News, 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Chicago Electric Club, 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Chicago Literary Bureau, 1891; 4 items (Box Series I-9)
    Frank Atkinson
  - Chicago Tribune, 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Chicago World's Congress of Electricians, 1893; 3 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Chicoine, Dr., 1896; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Chiek, I., 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Child, Charles T., 1899-1900; 4 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Chisholm, J. W., 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Christie, M. E., 1926; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Church of the Good Shepherd, 1915; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Cincinnati Commercial Club, 1898; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Cincinnati Edison Electric Company, 1900; 2 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Clapp, Dwight M., 1897; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Clark, Alvan & Sons Company, 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Clark, Charles P., 1896; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
    NY, New Haven & Hartford RR.
  - Clark, Henry, 1892; 4 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Clark, J. Shephard Company, 1897; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Clark, John S., 1899; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Clark, Latimer, 1889; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Clark, Lyman, 1905; 2 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Clark, Owen S., 1896; 3 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Clark, W. J., 1907; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Clark, William Edwin, 1894; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Clarke, Charles L., 1910-1930; 5 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Clarke, W. J., 1904; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Claycomb, F. P., 1905; 2 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Clayton, H. H., 1901; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Cleaves, Margaret A., 1895-1905; 9 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Clerk Maxwell Celebration, 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
    Cavendish Laboratory
  - Clifford, Harry E., 1903-1928; 13 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Clinton, Rathbone, 1910; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
    Industrial Investment Co.
  - Clohesey, Thomas F., 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Clop, Charles R., 1905; 2 items (Box Series I-9)
    M.I.T.
  - Clusterman, Francis J., 1905; 2 items (Box Series I-9)
    M.I.T. /Engineering Society
  - Cobb, C. M., 1908; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Cobb, L. J., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Coder, H. C., 1932; 1 item (Box Series I-9)
  - Codman, Ernest Amory, 1896-[1906]; 10 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Coffin, C. A., 1885-1926; 19 items (Box Series I-9)
  - Cohen, Louis, 1929; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Colcord, Samuel, 1923; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Cole, Edwin T., 1919; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Coleman Laboratories Corporation, 1916-1917; 2 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Coleman Ship and Pile Coppering Company, 1902; 6 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Coles, Stephen L., 1899; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Collier's Weekly, 1905; 2 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Collins, 1929; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Collins, A. Frederick, 1903-1911; 8 items (Box Series I-10)
    Collins Marine Wireless Telephone
  - Collins, [Chas.], 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Collins, Howard B., 1930; 2 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Collins, Spalding & Company, 1915-1929; 3 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Collum, M.H., 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Collum, William, 1903; 2 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Colne, C., 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Colonial Families of America, 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Columbia College * School of Mines, 1891-1900; 3 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Columbia Publishing Company, 1893; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Columbia University, 1898-1919; 4 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Columbia University. Department of Physics, 1929; 3 items (Box Series I-10)
    D. P. Mitchell
  - Combustion Utilities, 1927; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Comite Electrotechnique Italien, 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Commercial Club of Boston, 1887-1934; 23 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Commercial Club of Cincinnati, 1898-1903; 2 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Commercial Club of St. Louis, 1895-1897; 2 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Commission To Analyze Philadelphia Water, 1885; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Commission on Resucitation From Electric Shock, 1912; 8 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Committee for the Protection of Animal Experimentation, 1921; 4 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Committee of Electricity and Electrical Appliances, 1901; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
    Louisiana Purchase Exposition Company
  - Committee of Manufacturers, 1905-1907; 5 items (Box Series I-10)
  - [Committee to Honor Galileo], 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Commonwealth, 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
    F. E. Goodrich
  - Commonwealth of Australia. Postmaster General's Department, 1904; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts. Committee on Industrial Education, 1905; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts. County of Essex, 1898; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
    Clerk of the Court
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts. Executive Department, 1921; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
    Channing Cox, Govenor
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts. Metropolitan Park Commission, 1918; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Concrete and Constructional Engineering, 1907; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Concrete Institute, 1908; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Conde, C.A., 1924; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Congres International D'Electricite De 1932, 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Congress of Inventors and Manufacturers of Patented Inventions, 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Connecticut Building and Loan Association, 1897; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Conren, Joseph W., 1930; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Consolidated Zinc and Lead Company, 1900-1902; 7 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Consular Agency of Italy, 1899; 2 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Continental Insurance Company, 1895; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Conwell, E. L. & Company, 1931; 2 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Cook, Gustavus W., 1935; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Cook, Louis T., 1883; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Cook, Thos. & Son, 1924; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Cooll, G. M., 1928; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Coolidge and Carlson Architects, 1923-1930; 2 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Coolidge, Julian L., 1922; 2 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Coolidge, T. Jefferson, Jr., 1900-1929; 6 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Coolidge, W. D., 1908-1937; 8 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Cooper, Peter, 1903; 2 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Cooper, Simon, 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Cooper, William, 1903; 2 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Cormack, J. D., 1901; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
    International Engineering Congress
  - Cornell University * Sibley College, 1891-1903; 11 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Cornman, George W., Jr., 1896; 3 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Cosmopolitan Magazine, 1896-1904; 3 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Cottrell, F. G., 1912; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Coulston, Richard Inc., 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Council of the Institution of Engineers, 1898-1899; 3 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Coupler, 1924; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Cowles, Alfred, 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Cowles, James L., 1914; 3 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Cox & Sons Company, 1910; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Cox, F. P., 1917-1935; 9 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Craig, William, Jr., 1904; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Cram and Ferguson, 1920; 2 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Cramp, William and Sons Ship and Engine Building Company, 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Cramp, William, 1934; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Crawford, J. G., 1932; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Crehore, Albert C., 1895-1897; 2 items (Box Series I-10)
  - Crehore, A. C., Esq., 1901; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Creighton, Albert M., 1924; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Cress, George H., 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - "Crew of the Half Moon", 1915; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Crile, George W., 1912; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Crimora Manganese Corporation, 1917; 1 item (Box Series I-10)
  - Croasdale, Stuart, 1924; 1 item (Box Series I-11)
  - Croce, Joseph B., 1932; 1 item (Box Series I-11)
    Edison Elec. Illuminating Co.
  - Crocker, Francis B., 1891-1907; 17 items (Box Series I-11)
    Columbia Univ. /AIEE
  - Crockett, C. H., 1896; 1 item (Box Series I-11)
  - Chromaine Society, 1926; 1 item (Box Series I-11)
  - Crompton, R. E., 1905-1921; 30 items (Box Series I-11)
    Crompton Laboratory
  - Crompton, R. E., 1922-1927; 31 items (Box Series I-11)
  - Crompton, R. E., 1928-1936; 27 items (Box Series I-11)
  - Crosbie-MacDonald Insurance, 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-11)
  - Crosby, Henry A., 1915-1916; 5 items (Box Series I-11)
  - Crosby, Oscar T., 1902-1905; 4 items (Box Series I-1)
  - Crosley Radio Corporation, 1924; 2 items (Box Series I-11)
    George Lewis
  - Cross, C. R., 1895-1920; 26 items (Box Series I-11)
    M.I.T./ Rumford Committee
  - Crossdill, C. Watson, 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-11)
  - Crossin & Tucker Jewelers, 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-11)
    F. Richardson
  - Crouse, J. Robert, 1910-1914; 8 items (Box Series I-11)
    Society for Electrical Development
  - Crowe, B. F., 1932; 1 item (Box Series I-11)
  - Crowley, Alexander, 1916; 2 items (Box Series I-11)
  - Cuff, William, 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-11)
  - Culliton, John, 1891-1892; 3 items (Box Series I-11)
  - Culver, W. S., 1929; 3 items (Box Series I-11)
  - Cummings, G. F., 1924; 1 item (Box Series I-11)
  - Cunard Steam Ship Company, Ltd., 1924; 1 item (Box Series I-11)
  - Cupples & Schoenhof, 1903; 1 item (Box Series I-11)
  - Curley, James M., 1917-1918; 2 items (Box Series I-11)
    Mayor of Boston
  - Currier, Roland E., 1921; 1 item (Box Series I-11)
  - Curtis, Charles G., 1909-1911; 3 items (Box Series I-11)
    International Curtis Marine Turbine Co.
  - Curtis, Leonard, 1898; 1 item (Box Series I-11)
  - Curtis, Lizzi, 1897; 4 items (Box Series I-11)
  - Curtis, Richard C., 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-11)
  - Cushing, Harvey, MD, 1927-1935; 3 items (Box Series I-11)
  - Cutter, George, 1887-1936; 17 items (Box Series I-11)
  - Cycle and Automobile Trade Journal, 1901; 2 items (Box Series I-11)
  - Czechoslovak Legation, 1926; 2 items (Box Series I-11)
    Jaroslav Lipa
  - Dachneske, Carl, 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Dabney, Charles W., 1899; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
    University of Tennessee, Pres.
  - Dahl, G. C., 1934; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Dahlgren, C. B., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Dahlin, C. T., 1929; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Daily Princetonian, 1909; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
    L. R. Kendrick
  - Dallin, Cyrus E., 1922; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Dalph, J. H., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Damon, W. Ward, 1915; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
    Nomad Supply Company
  - Dana, Paul, Esq., 1901; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
    The Sun
  - Danielian, Noobor R., 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Danielson, E., 1899-1901; 2 items (Box Series I-12)
  - Dans, Paul, 1900; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Darke, J.M., 1899; 3 items (Box Series I-12)
    American Chemical Society Membership
  - Darling, Henry W., 1923; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Darling, Nelson J., 1923-1935; 11 items (Box Series I-12)
  - Darlington, F., 1916; 2 items (Box Series I-12)
    Am. Inst.of Electrical Engineers
  - Darnnlaedsis, L., 1898; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Darrah, J. N., 1899; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Davenport, B. F., 1900; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
    American Chemical Society
  - Davenport, Charles B., 1935; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Davenport, G. W., 1896-1900; 3 items (Box Series I-12)
  - Davidson, J. B., 1914; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Davis, Albert G., 1923-1931; 8 items (Box Series I-12)
  - Davis, Charles B., 1902-1923; 4 items (Box Series I-12)
  - Davis, Charles H., 1900-1901; 4 items (Box Series I-12)
  - Davis, Daniel, 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Davis, Frederick W. & Company, 1907; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Davis, Russell, 1932; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Davis, W. M., 1912-1921; 4 items (Box Series I-12)
    American Geographical Society of New York
  - Dawson, W. F., 1923; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Deal, Lemuel J., 1924; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Debule, T. I., 1916; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - DeFerranti Reception Committee, 1924; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
    John W. Lieb
  - DeForest, Lee, 1920-1925; 2 items (Box Series I-12)
  - DeIrizar, P.R., 1925; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
    Ingeniero Electricista Habana
  - DeKhotinsky, A., 1893; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
    Germania Electric Company
  - DeLand, Fred, 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
    Electric World
  - Delphey, Eden V., 1902; 3 items (Box Series I-12)
  - Delaware and Hudson Company, 1904; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Delaware & Hudson Railroad Company, 1913; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - DeNardi, Charles, 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Dennis, A. W. and Company, 1916; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Dennison Manufacturing Company, 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Department of Building Construction, 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Derby, George, 1909-1914; 2 items (Box Series I-12)
    National Cyclopedia of American Biography
  - Dercum, Elizabeth, 1929; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Dercum, Francis X., 1916-1929; 8 items (Box Series I-12)
  - Detroit Free Press, 1925; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Deutsches Museum, 1912-1935; 12 items (Box Series I-12)
  - Devers, Philip K., 1917-1933; 4 items (Box Series I-12)
  - Devine, York & Lincoln, 1930; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Dickerson, Mary C., 1916-1917; 3 items (Box Series I-12)
    American Museum of Natural History
  - Dickey, Glen D., 1893; 2 items (Box Series I-12)
  - Dieny, Paul, 1908; 10 items (Box Series I-12)
    International Exhibition of the Applications of Electricity
  - Dill, Herbert E., 1893; 2 items (Box Series I-12)
  - Dilworth, May, 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Discrola, Inc., 1922; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
    C. Francis Jenkins
  - Doane, S. E., 1905-1928; 13 items (Box Series I-12)
  - Dodd, David, 1909; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Dodd, T. W., 1912; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
    Dodd & Struthers
  - Dodd, Walter J., 1909-1914; 2 items (Box Series I-12)
    Massachusetts General Hospital
  - Doherty, Henry L., 1910; 2 items (Box Series I-12)
  - Doherty, Henry L. & Company, 1912-1924; 6 items (Box Series I-12)
  - Dolbear, A. E., 1896-1900; 4 items (Box Series I-12)
    Tufts College
  - Donovan, Benedict, 1899; 2 items (Box Series I-12)
  - Donovan, Dan P., 1901; 2 items (Box Series I-12)
  - Donaldson, Walter A., 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Dooley, Paul, 1919; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Doolittle, S. H., 1929; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Doubleday, Doran & Company, 1930; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
    World's Work
  - Doubleday, Page and Company, 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Douglas, Daryl, 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Douglas, James, 1916; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Douglass, R. W., 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
  - Dow, Alex, 1901-1908; 9 items (Box Series I-12)
    Edison Illuminating Cos.
  - Draper, Paul A., 1920; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
    U.S. Dept of the Interior. Bureau of Mines
  - Dreiser, Theodore, 1909; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
    The Delineator, Editor
  - DuBois, Howard W., 1902-1917; 39 items (Box Series I-12)
  - DuBois, L. A., 1914; 1 item (Box Series I-12)
    DuPont de Nemours Powders Co. `
  - Duddell, W., 1901; 3 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Dudgeon, Richard, 1907; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
  - Dudgeou, Burt, 1896; 2 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Dudley, Charles B., 1892; 2 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Duncan, Louis, 1891; 2 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Duncan, Robert Kennedy, 1906; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
  - Duncan, Thomas, 1898; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
    Fort Wayne Elec. Co.
  - Dunham, A. C., 1912-1916; 6 items (Box Series I-13)
    Hartford Elec. Light Co.
  - Dunkerley, Gordon, 1907; 2 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Dunlap, John R., 1896; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
  - Dunlop, D. M., 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
  - Dunn, Gano S., 1900-1926; 25 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Dustin, Charles E., 1901-1902; 4 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Dwight, R. H. W., 1904-1905; 3 items (Box Series I-13)
    National Express Co.
  - Dwight, Theodore, 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
  - Dwyer, E. F., 1898; 3 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Dyer, Richard N., 1912-1914; 6 items (Box Series I-13)
    A.I.E.E. Edison Medal Comm.
  - Eaboll, F. J., 1922; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
  - Eastern Association of Physics Teachers, 1925; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
    N. Henry Black
  - Eastern-Cahill Telharmonic Company, 1907; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
    Frederick Todd
  - Eastman, George, 1928-1931; 4 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Eayrs, Winslow, 1891-1892; 2 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Eddy, H. T., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
  - Edgar, Charles L., 1898-1927; 16 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Edgcumbe, K., 1929; 2 items (Box Series I-13)
    Colindale Works. London
  - Edgerly & Crocker, 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
  - Edison Club, 1920; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
    Ketcham, V. A.
  - Edison Electric Appliance Company, Inc., 1925; 3 items (Box Series I-13)
    H. J. Mauger
  - Edison Institute, 1929-1933; 2 items (Box Series I-13)
    James W. Bishop
  - Edison Pioneers, 1929; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
    J. W. Lieb
  - Edison, Charles, 1928-1931; 2 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Edison, Thomas A., 1899- 1931; 12 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Edison, Mrs. Thomas A., 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
  - Edmonds, Franklin S., 1929; 2 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Edson, E. R., 1903-1904; 5 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Educational Press of New York, 1924; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
    Irving Jay Rogers
  - Educational Review, 1927; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
  - Education Service Bulletin, [1921?]; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
  - Edwards, Levi T., 1899-1900; 5 items (Box Series I-13)
    Haverford College. Dept. of Engineering
  - Eglin, William C. L., 1921-1926; 8 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Eickemeyer, George, 1901; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
  - Eilers, Roy and Fern, 1925; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
  - Electric Bond and Share Securities Corporation, 1929; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
    E. W. Hill15
  - Electric Club of Cleveland, 1897-1905; 5 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Electric Club Journal, 1904; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
    J. H. Smith
  - Electric Corporation, 1898-1907; 6 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Electric Foreman's Association, 1892; 3 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Electric Home Supply Company, 1908; 2 items (Box Series I-13)
    Max Lowenthal
  - Electric Journal, 1906; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
  - Electric Launch and Navigation Company, 1893-1896; 5 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Electric Lighting Company of Mobile, 1898-1899; 3 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Electric Pipe Bending Company, 1891-1892; 2 items (Box Series I-13)
    F. P. Royce
  - Electric Potential Club, 1895-1896; 9 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Electric Power, 1895-1898; 6 items (Box Series I-13)
    Max Osterberg, Assoc. Editor
  - Electric Storage Battery Company, 1897-1898; 2 items (Box Series I-13)
  - Electric Welding, 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-13)
    James Caldwell
  - Electric Welding Company, LTD, 1902-1905; 5 items (Box Series I-13)
    Reginald I. Wallis-Jones
  - Electrical Age, 1892-1907; 10 items (Box Series I-14)
  - Electrical Association of New York, 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-14)
  - Electrical Doings, 1896; 1 item (Box Series I-14)
  - Electrical Engineer, 1891-1893; 34 items (Box Series I-14)
    Thomas C. Martin & J. Wetzler
  - Electrical Engineer, 1894-1896; 26 items (Box Series I-14)
    *See also Electrical World and Electrical Engineer
  - Electrical Engineer, 1897-1903; 25 items (Box Series I-14)